

SUHAIB AHMAD

Full-Stack Web Developer

An experienced individual who have what it takes to fulfill any of many positions related to the software development process. Into coding, but perusing an agenda that includes a minimum of a brief introduction & experience for every part of software development work. Currently, I am working as a frontend dev based in Jordan and open for a full-time opportunity anywhere worldwide.



SuhaibAhmadAi@hotmail.com

Makkahwi

<u>()</u> +6011-280-94-804

(7) O Makkahwi

Experiences

Frontend Developer

Full-Timer

ArabWork | Amman, Jordan

2 Months Jun 2022 - Present

Frontend Developer

Full-Timer

LuxTag | Cyberjaya, Malaysia

6 Months
May - Oct 2021

Full-Stack Developer

Intern

LuxTag | Cyberjaya, Malaysia

6 Months Nov 2020 - Apr 2021

Full-Stack Developer

Part-Timer

AIS School | KL, Malaysia

12 Months Sep 2019 - Aug 2020

Full-Stack Developer

Freelancer Malaysia 2 Years Sep 2019 - Present

Wordpress Developer

Freelancer Malaysia 3 Years Oct 2015 - Apr 2019

Skills



React.Js



Vue.Js



Node.Js



Express.Js



Laravel



Django



Wordpress



PostgreSQL



VS Code

MySQL



JavaScript

GitHub



jQuery

Docker



JSON



Python



PHP



HTML



CSS



Bootstrap



Agile



SCRUM



Kanban



REST API

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science

International Islamic University Malaysia | May 2021

Specialized in Data Science and Computational Intelligence